Let them see you.
The Watchers is a fantasy, horror, mystery film
directed by Ishana Night Shyamalan.
A young artist gets stranded in an extensive, immaculate forest in western Ireland, where, after finding
shelter, she becomes trapped alongside three strangers, stalked by mysterious creatures each night.
Mina / Lucy, played by Dakota Fanning.
Ciara, played by Georgina Campbell.
Madeline, played by Olwen Fouéré.
Daniel, played by Oliver Finnegan.
John, played by Alistair Brammer.
Kilmartin, played by John Lynch.
The Watchers is a 2024 American supernatural horror fantasy film written for the screen and
directed by Ishana Night Shyamalan in her directorial debut, produced by her father M.
Night Shyamalan, and based on the 2021 novel by A.
It stars Dakota Fanning, Georgina Campbell, Olwen Fouéré, Hannah Howland, and Oliver Finnegan, and follows
Mina, a 28-year-old artist who becomes trapped in a vast, untouched forest in the west of Ireland.
Seeking shelter, she becomes trapped alongside three strangers who
are stalked by mysterious creatures every night.
The Watchers was released theatrically in the United States by Warner Bros.
Pictures on June 7, 2024.
The film received negative reviews from critics
and grossed $33 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
shapeshifting, bunker, forest, shelter.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.